appmobi.com 2012-05-10

# Privacy Policy

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how appMobi treats personal information that appMobi collects and receives, including information related to your past use of appMobi products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that appMobi does not own or control, or to people that appMobi does not employ or manage. In addition, certain appMobi associated companies have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by visiting the websites of those companies.

 **Information Collection and Use**

 **General**

  *  **appMobi never stores sensitive financial information** , such as credit card information on its servers. When you give appMobi your credit card information in order to purchase a product or service, we never store that information after the transaction has been processed. 
  * appMobi collects personal information when you register with appMobi, when you use appMobi products or services, when you visit appMobi pages or the pages of certain appMobi partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. appMobi may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with appMobi and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * appMobi collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.
  * appMobi automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, appMobi cookie information, and the page you request.
  * appMobi uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

 **Children**

  * When a child under age 13 attempts to register with appMobi, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a appMobi Family Account to obtain parental permission.
  * appMobi will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission.
  * appMobi does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion.

 **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * appMobi does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with appMobi under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help appMobi communicate with you about offers from appMobi and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    * We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing appMobi to collect and use their child's information without consenting to appMobi sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes;
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of appMobi' terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if appMobi is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, appMobi will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * appMobi displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.
    * appMobi does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
    * appMobi advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).
  * appMobi works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed reference links.

 **Cookies**

  * appMobi may set and access appMobi cookies on your computer.
  * appMobi lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to appMobi' cookies.
  * appMobi uses web beacons to access appMobi cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with appMobi products and services.

 **Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

 **General**

  * You can edit your appMobi Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time.
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the appMobi service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the appMobi Newsletter, that are considered part of your appMobi account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your appMobi account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Any or all of the information you provided while your account was active might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

 **Children  **

  * Parents can review, edit, and delete information relating to their child's appMobi account using tools offered by appMobi Family Accounts.
  * If a parent chooses not to allow us to further collect or use a child's information, parents enrolled in appMobi Family Accounts can delete their child's account by signing into that child's account and then visiting our Account Deletion page. Any or all of the information you provided while your account was active might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

 **Confidentiality and Security  **

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * appMobi may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your appMobi account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
